Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Volume XLVIII, issued 1951
  - 2. General catalogue issue, January 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 3. Master of Arts in Teaching, January 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 4. Harvard Summer School, Arts, Sciences, Education, preliminary announcement, January 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, April 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 6. Preliminary announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1951-1952, April 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 7. The Law School, courses of instruction, academic year, 1951-1952, May 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 8. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in medical sciences, May 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 9. Graduate School of Business Administration, academic year 1951-1952, May 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 10. Summer School of Arts and Sciences, and of Education, 1951, May 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 11. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1951-1952, June 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 12. Division of Engineering Sciences, catalogue and announcement of the courses of instruction and research for the year 1951-1952, June 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 13. Graduate School of Education, preliminary announcement of the courses of instruction for 1951-1952, June 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 14. Asiatic studies at Harvard University, June 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 15. The Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1950-1951, with an announcement for 1951-1952, July 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 16. Department of Social Relations, July 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 17. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, July 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 18. The Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction for the year 1951-1952, August 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 19. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1951-1952, August 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 20. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1951-1952, September 1, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 21. Final announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1951-1952, September 10, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 22. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, September 14, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 23. Harvard Divinity School, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the year 1950-1951, September 20, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 24. Financial report to the Board of Overseers of Harvard College for the fiscal year 1950-1951, September 28, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 25. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, October 15, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
  - 26. The Harvard School of Dental Medicine, aims, general information, announcement of courses, October 30, 1951 (HU 75.25 Box 87)
- Volume XLIX, issued 1952
  - 1. Courses in general education, 1951-1952, January 4, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 2. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1952, January 14, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 3. General catalogue issue, January 25, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 4. A pamphlet about Harvard for the prospective undergraduate, January 31, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 5. The Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1951-1952, with an announcement for 1952-1953, March 14, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 6. Summer School of Arts and Sciences, and of Education, 1952, March 31, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 7. The Law School, courses of instruction, academic year 1952-1953, April 1, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 8. Harvard Divinity School, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the year 1951-1952, April 7, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 9. Rules relating to College studies, April 10, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 10. Issue containing the report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments for 1948-1949, April 30, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 11. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1952-1953, May 12, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 12. Graduate School of Business Administration, academic year 1952-1953, May 26, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 13. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1952-1953, May 29, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 14. The Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction for the year 1952-1953, June 2, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 15. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in medical sciences, June 9, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 16. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1952-1953, June 30, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 17. Asiatic studies at Harvard University, June 24, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 18. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, June 30, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 19. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1952-1953, August 29, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 20. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences of Harvard University, 1952-1953, September 15, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 21. Courses in general education, 1952-1953, September 30, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 22. Master of Arts in Teaching, October 15, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 23. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, October 24, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 24. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, November 20, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
  - 25. Master of Arts in Teaching, December 22, 1952 (HU 75.25 Box 88)
- Volume L, issued 1953
  - 1. Division of Applied Science, covering the fields of applied mathematics, applied physics, engineering, 1953-1954, January 7, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 2. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1953, January 21, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 3. General catalogue issue, March 2, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 90)
  - 4. The Harvard School of Dental Medicine, aims, general information, announcement of courses, March 17, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 5. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, March 31, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 6. Rules relating to College studies, April 8, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 7. The Law School, courses of instruction, academic year 1953-1954, April 15, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 8. Studies in language and communication, a special announcement of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, April 22, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 9. The Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1952-1953, with an announcement for 1953-1954, April 24, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 90)
  - 10. Harvard Divinity School, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the year 1952-1953, May 14, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 11. Graduate School of Business Administration, academic year, 1953-1954, May 28, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 12. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1953-1954, June 23, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 13. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1953-1954, July 7, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 14. The Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction for the year 1953-1954, July 14, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 15. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, July 21, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 16. Asiatic studies at Harvard University, July 28, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 17. Master of Arts in Teaching, August 12, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 18. Department of Social Relations, August 19, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 19. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1953-1954, August 21, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 20. Courses in general education, 1953-1954, August 24, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 21. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1953-1954, August 25, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 22. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences of Harvard University, September 16, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 23. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, September 30, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 24. Graduate School in Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in medical sciences, November 2, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
  - 25. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, November 4, 1953 (HU 75.25 Box 89)
    Misprinted on cover as Vol. XL, no. 25."
- Volume LI, issued 1954
  - 1. Division of Applied Science, general announcement, 1953-1954, January 2, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 2. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1954, January 15, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 3. General catalogue issue, 1953, January 30, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 92)
  - 4. Harvard Summer School, final catalogue, 1954, March 17, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 5. The Law School, courses of instruction, academic year 1954-1955, March 31, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 6. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1949-1950, April 2, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 92)
  - 7. Rules relating to College studies, 1954, April 1, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 8. Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1953-1954, with announcement for 1954-1955, April 5, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 9. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1950-1951, April 20, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 92)
  - 10. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, aims, general information, announcement of courses, 1954-1955, May 5, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 11. Graduate School of Design, courses in architecture, landscape architecture, city and regional planning, May 19, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 12. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1954-1955, May 26, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 13. Harvard Divinity School, annual lectures and book reviews, vol. 19, 1953-1954, June 1, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 92)
  - 14. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, June 8, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 15. Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction for the year 1954-1955, June 30, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 16. Instruction in oceanography offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1954, June 25, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 17. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1954-1955, June 27, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 18. Graduate School of Public Administration, 1954, June 29, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 19. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, higher degrees in medical sciences, July 28, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 20. Courses in general education, 1954-1955, August 24, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 21. Asiatic studies at Harvard University, 1954-1955, July 26, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 22. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1954-1955, August 31, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 23. Divinity School, 1954-1955, September 8, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 24. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, general announcement, 1954-1955, September 10, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 25. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1951-1952, August 27, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 92)
  - 26. Master of Arts in Teaching, September 17, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 27. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, September 24, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 28. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, October 1, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 91)
  - 29. General catalogue issue, 1954-1955, November 30, 1954 (HU 75.25 Box 92)
- Volume LII, issued 1955
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 24. Divinity School, September 15, 1955.
  - 1. Division of Applied Science, 1953-1954, January 3, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 2. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1955, January 15, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 3. Regional studies, Soviet Union, Middle East, East Asia, 1955-1956, January 24, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 4. Biochemical sciences, 1954-1955, March 1, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 5. The Law School, 1955-1956, April 1, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 6. Harvard Summer School, final catalogue, 1955, March 29, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 7. Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1954-1955, April 15, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 8. Rules relating to College studies, April 22, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 9. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1955-1956, April 29, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 10. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1955-1956, May 31, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 11. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, May 4, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 12. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1952-1953, May 27, 1955 (HU 72.25 Box 94)
    Mis-numbered on cover as 11.
  - 13. The Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction for the year 1955-1956, June 27, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 14. Graduate School of Education, 1955-1956, June 30, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 15. Asiatic studies at Harvard University, 1955-1956, June 30, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 16. Graduate School of Public Administration, 1955-1956, June 24, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 17. Department of Social Relations, June 28, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 18. The Graduate School of Design, July 28, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 19. Courses in general education, 1955-1956, July 29, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 20. Courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1955-1956, August 31, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 21. Harvard Divinity School, annual lectures and book reviews, volume number 20, 1954-1955, August 29, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 22. Higher degrees in medical sciences, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1955, September 16, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 23. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1955-1956, August 30, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 25. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, 1955-1956, September 12, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 26. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, September 12, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
  - 27. General catalogue issue, October 21, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 94)
  - 28. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1953-1954, October 31, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 94)
  - 29. Engineering in Harvard College, 1955-1956, November 30, 1955 (HU 75.25 Box 93)
- Volume LIII, issued 1956
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1956, January 19, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 2. Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1955-1956, January 2, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 3. Harvard Summer School, final catalogue, 1956, March 29, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 4. Rules relating to College studies, 1956, March 15, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 5. The catalogue of the Law School, 1956-1957, April 2, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 6. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1956-1957, April 15, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 7. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, May 26, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 8. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1956-1957, April 30, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 9. Graduate School of Education, 1956-1957, May 24, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 10. Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction, 1956-1957, June 29, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 11. Graduate School of Public Administration, 1956-1957, June 25, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 12. Harvard Divinity School, 1956-1957, July 30, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 13. Courses in general education, 1956-1957, July 31, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 14. Courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1956-1957, August 31, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 15. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1956-1957, September 6, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 16. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, September 10, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 17. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, 1956-1957, September 12, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 18. Scholarship, beneficiary aid and loan funds of Harvard College, 1956-1957, September 17, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 19. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, annual lectures and book reviews, volume number 21, 1955-1956, November 5, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 20. Master of Arts in Teaching, November 19, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 21. Division of Engineering and Applied Physics, November 26, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 22. Master of Education, December 17, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 23. Higher degrees in medical sciences, December 17, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
  - 24. General catalogue issue, 1956-1957, December 26, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 96)
  - 25. Reports of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1954-1955, December 28, 1956 (HU 75.25 Box 95)
- Volume LIV, issued 1957
  - 1. Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1957, January 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 2. Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1956-1957, February 27, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 3. Harvard Summer School, final catalogue, 1957, March 29, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 4. The catalogue of the Law School, 1957-1958, April 1, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, 1957, April 8, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 6. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1957-1958, April 15, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 7. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, annual lectures and book reviews, volume number 22, 1956-1957, April 30, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 8. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1957-1958, March 15, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 9. Harvard Divinity School, 1957-1958, May 20, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 10. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Department of Biology, May 27, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 11. Studies in the freshman year, including an announcement of the program in general education, June 3, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 12. Graduate School of Education, 1957-1958, June 24, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 13. Department of Social Relations, June 28, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 14. Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction, 1957-1958, July 29, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 15. Graduate School of Public Administration, 1957-1958, August 5, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 16. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1957-1958, August 12, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 17. Courses in general education, 1957-1958, August 23, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 18. The Graduate School of Design, August 26, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 19. Courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1957-1958, September 4, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 20. Master of Education, teaching in elementary schools, 1957-1958, September 5, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 21. Master of Arts in Teaching, 1957-1958, September 6, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 22. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, 1957-1958, September 25, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 23. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, 1957, September 27, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 24. Scholarship, beneficiary aid and loan funds of Harvard College, 1957-1958, November 15, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
  - 25. General catalogue issue, 1957-1958, November 29, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 98)
  - 26. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1955-1956, December 30, 1957 (HU 75.25 Box 97)
- Volume LV, issued 1958
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 23. Reports of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, September 28, 1960.
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1958, January 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 2. Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1957-1958, February 27, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 3. Harvard Summer School, final catalogue, 1958, March 31, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 4. The Law School of Harvard University, catalogue for 1958-1959, April 1, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, 1958, April 7, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 6. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1958-1959, April 15, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 7. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, lectures and book reviews, volume number 23, 1957-1958, April 25, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 8. Division of Engineering and Applied Physics, 1958, May 16, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 9. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1958-1959, May 23, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 10. Engineering in Harvard College, 1958-1959, May 26, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 11. Studies in the freshman year, including a description of the program in general education, June 13, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 12. Harvard Divinity School, 1958-1959, June 20, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 13. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1958-1959, June 27, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 14. Graduate School of Public Administration, 1958-1959, July 11, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 15. Graduate School of Education, 1958-1959, August 8. 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 16. Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction, 1958-1959, August 11, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 17. Master of Arts in Teaching, teaching in secondary schools, August 14, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 18. Master of Education, teaching in elementary schools, August 15, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 19. Courses in general education, 1958-1959, September 2, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 20. Courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1958-1959, September 2, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 21. Information about Harvard College for prospective students, September 10, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 22. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, 1958-1959, September 16, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 99)
  - 24. General catalogue issue, 1958-1959, November 25, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 25. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1956-1957, December 30, 1958 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
- Volume LVI, issued 1959
  - 1. Harvard Summer School, preliminary announcement, 1959, January 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 2. Harvard Medical School and School of Dental Medicine, 1958-1959, February 16, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 3. Harvard Summer School, final catalogue, 1959,March 31, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 4. The Law School, catalogue for 1959-1960, April 1, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, 1959, April 7, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 6. Harvard School of Dental Medicine, 1959-1960, April 21, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 7. Biochemical sciences, 1959-1960, April 22, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 8. Scholarship, beneficiary aid and loan funds of Harvard College, 1959, May 1, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 9. Advanced standing at Harvard College, May 29, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 10. Harvard School of Public Health, courses of instruction, 1959-1960, June 29, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 11. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1959-1960, July 15, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 12. Graduate School of Public Administration, 1959-1960, July 17, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 13. Studies in the freshman year, including a description of the program in general education, July 20, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 14. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1959-1960, July 22, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 15. The Graduate School of Education, 1959-1960, July 29, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 16. Harvard Divinity School, 1959-1960, July 30, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 17. Department of Social Relations, July 31, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 18. Master of Arts in Teaching, teaching in secondary schools, 1959-1960, August 14, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 19. Information about Harvard College for propspective students, August 17, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 20. Courses in general education, 1959-1960, August 25, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)
  - 21. Master of Education, teaching in elementary schools, August 28, 1959 (HU 75.25 Box 100)